Abdallah Ashraf



Front-End Developer (React.js)

Portfolio

Contact

Address: Tanta, AlGhrbiya. Phone: +201110991895

LinkedIn



Education

Institute: New Cairo Academy Faculty: Computer Science Graduated: In August 2021

Grade: "Good", Graduation Project "Employee Attendance "with grade "V.Good".

Courses

PHP Full Sack Diploma
- [Russian Cultural Center] •
[From (8/2022) To (Right now)].

Full Stack JavaScript and Front-End web Development

- [Udemy] • [From (5/2022) To (11/2022)].

HTML, CSS and JavaScript - [Sololearn] • [From (10/2022)

To (11/2022)].

Other Skills

Have the ability to learn new skills.

Creative and able to accept risk & find solutions.

Ambitious, with good communication skills with different types of people.

- ✓ Available Upon Request.
- ✓ I ended military service.
- ✓ Last update 15/12/2022.

Professional Summary

As student, I made a project on the Employee Attendance System (ERP), and I used these techniques during the project:

1-Front-end Developer using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js and I worked during this period on some other projects in which I used these mentioned languages such as: GYM Store, Music Store and some other projects.

2- Back-end Developer using: SQL Server Database and dot.net C In fact, my colleague in the project helped me connect the databases to the project because my experience in backend in this period was average. But I love the front-end path, so I developed myself on it.

3-system analyses I also used these charts:

Scenario Diagram, Use Cases Diagram, Flowchart Diagram, DFD Diagram, Context Diagram, Activity Diagram and ERD Diagram & Schema.

Work Experience

From 12-10-2020 to 16-5-2021

[Employee Attendance System] • [Using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js and SQL Server Database] • [Graduation project].

From 1-12-2022 to 20-12-2022

[Restaurant Food] • [Using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and React.js] • [A project for a restaurant food].

From 1-8-2021 to 20-10-2021

[Admin dashboard] • [Using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and React.js] • [Admin dashboard: analytics].

From 20-11-2022 to 25-11-2022

[Portfolio] • [Using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and React.js]

• [A personal project to raise my projects on it].

Relevant Skills

Front-end Experience:	Back-end Experience:
- HTML, CSS [2Year].	- PHP [Basics].
- JavaScript [1Year].	- MySQL [Basics].
- JQuery & Bootstrap [1Year].	- SQL Server [intermediate].
- React.js [intermediate].	- Laravel [Basics].